rankandstyle.com 2016-03-26

# Rank & Style | Privacy Policy

Rank & Style takes your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy policies that apply to your use of RankandStyle.com (the “Website”) and the type of information we collect and receive from you when you use RankandStyle.com or sign up for our newsletters. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting or using this Website in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.

* Personal Information  
In order to deliver our newsletters to you, and for other purposes deemed necessary for use by Rank & Style, we need your email address. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as required to provide you with Rank & Style content. Rank & Style will never sell, rent, or share your personal information, including your email address, to any third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may contact you about products, services or events that are relevant to your interests. 

* Other Information  
We may request additional information such as age, buying preferences, or other demographic or profile information. We use this information to customize our content and improve your experience on our Website. We may also share this information with third parties, such as advertisers, but only in aggregate, anonymous form. We will not share information with third parties that personally identifies you or anyone else in any way. In addition, Rank & Style has implemented Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

* Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
Rank & Style collects non-personally identifiable information automatically when you visit our Website. Non-personally identifiable information is information that is not used nor intended to be used to personally identify an individual and is not associated with nor linked to personal information. Examples of such information includes but is not limited to: how much time users spend on our Website, what pages they view, what sites brought them to our Website, what keywords were they searching, browser type, browser language, and user city. 

* Use of Information.   
We will use your personal information to:  
• Provide you with Rank & Style content, including personalizing our content for you (which may include disclosing information to third party vendors who help us provide our content or the Website);  
• Market our products and services to you that we believe may be of interest to you.  
• Respond to your requests, resolve disputes and/or troubleshoot problems;  
• Improve the quality of the Website and the content; and  
• Communicate with you about the Website and the content.  

In addition, we may aggregate your non-personally identifiable information with the non-personally identifiable information of others and share that aggregated information with third parties without restriction.

* Review and Access  
Upon request, Rank & Style will provide you with a summary of the information we've collected about you, and the opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

* Subscribing to Our Newsletter

When you sign up to become a user through our Website, you have the option to choose to subscribe to our newsletter list. However, if you sign up using your Facebook account, you will automatically be subscribed to our newsletter list. In any case, you can unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions below.

* How to Unsubscribe  
You can unsubscribe from receiving Rank & Style emails at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in the footer of any Rank & Style email and following the instructions.

* Cookies  
Like most other websites, we use Cookies on the Website. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's web browser while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience. Persistent Cookies can be removed or blocked by following the help file directions in your Internet browser. If you elect to block Cookies, you may not be able to access certain personalized sections of our Website. We also use log files and Cookies to improve the quality of our Website; to keep track of your login name, passwords, and pages you have visited on the Website; and to tailor content to your interests and to personalize the Website on your behalf.

In addition, third-party vendors also use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies or other third-party identifiers together. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

* Links to Third Party Sites; Affiliate Relationships; Advertising  

Our Website may contain content or links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over, do not review, and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other websites. When you click on such a link, you will leave our Website and go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect personal information or anonymous information from you. The Website may also contain links to other websites controlled by us but which operate under different privacy policies. Please review the privacy policy of any new site you visit.

Purchases made through third party retailers’ sites linked to our Website are subject to the policies and procedures of those sites. Order fulfillment and customer service relating to orders placed at any of those third party sites, including the collection of applicable sales taxes, are the sole responsibility of such sites. Any concerns regarding order fulfillment, customer service, privacy policies or other issues relating to these third party retail sites should be directed to the administrator of the Website.

We may use third parties to serve ads on the site. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our site (but not your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number). They do this by using cookies or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or pixel tags in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of Cookies and other technologies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).   

We've also implemented certain Google Analytics Advertising features. Users can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising features through [Google Analytics' Opt-out Browser](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

* Sale or Transfer  
In some cases, Rank & Style may choose to sell or transfer assets to a third party. In the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, liquidation, receivership, sale or transfer of Rank & Style’s assets, or similar transaction, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such transaction. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the new entity follows this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal Information, as and to the extent required by applicable law.

* Security  
We take reasonable effort to protect your personal information that is stored on our database. Access to your personal information is limited to our authorized staff who need that information to perform their job functions.

* Amendments  
Rank & Style may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we do, we'll be sure to update these policies so please check back often if you are interested.

* Contact Us  
If you have questions about this policy, or about the Website, please contact us.
